[
    {"question":"In which year was Honda founded?", "answer":"1948"},
    {"question":"In which year did Henry Ford first launch his mass production plant for the Model T?", "answer":"12-May"},
    {"question":"In which year was Volvo founded?", "answer":"1927"},
    {"question":"In which year did the Civic Hybrid debut?", "answer":"2003"},
    {"question":"In which year was Skoda founded?", "answer":"1940"},
    {"question":"In which town was the Austin-Healey Sprite produced?", "answer":"Gremlin"},
    {"question":"In which year was Citreon founded?", "answer":"1919"},
    {"question":"In which year was Mercedes-Benz founded?", "answer":"2019"},
    {"question":"In which UK town is the Land Rover plant?", "answer":"Solihull"},
    {"question":"n which year did Ford establish Vauxhall Motors in the UK?", "answer":"1960"},
    {"question":"In which year was GM founded?", "answer":"1908"},
    {"question":"In which year was the Austin Maestro launched?", "answer":"1983"}
   
  ]